Abraham Ribicoff Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellany, 1927-1981 (Box 644-676)
  - Voting record (Box 644)
    - Record
      - 1974-1980, (8 folders) (Box 645)
    - Legislative record
    - Senate voting record, 96th Congress, (4 folders) (Box 646)
    - Bills supported by AAR, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box 647, Box 648)
  - Biographical information, (18 folders); (27 folders) (Box 649)
  - Articles by and about AAR, (53 folders); (4 folders) (Box 650, Box 651)
  - Reports
    - Managing the federal government, the role of the president, (5 folders); (8 folders) (Box 652)
    - Jefferson-Jackson-Bailey Dinner, 1980, Mar. (Box 653)
    - Libyan-U.S. relations, 1979
    - Senate Office Systems Research Project, 1977, (5 folders)
    - United Nations
    - Voter attitudes in Connecticut, 1980, May
  - Personal (nonpolitical) (Box 654)
    - Award
    - “Abe's Town”
    - Endorsements
    - High school yearbook, 1927
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Books (Box 655)
      - Politics: The American Way, 1966-1978, (2 folders)
      - The American Medical Machine, 1970-1973, (3 folders)
      - America Can Make It, 1972-1973, (4 folders)
      - By George Goodwin, 1969-1975, (3 folders) (Box 656)
      - Miscellaneous publishing
    - Travel
      - 1951-1971, (6 folders)
      - 1971-1978, (13 folders) (Box 657)
      - 1978-1979, (7 folders) (Box 658)
    - Sponsorships
      - 1963-1965, (6 folders)
      - 1966-1967, (4 folders) (Box 659)
    - Retirement letters, 1979-1980, (7 folders)
    - Correspondence management system (Box 660)
      - Encyclopedia
      - Pre-CMS sample letters
      - CMS index (Box 661)
        - A-G
        - C-Ch
      - Index (Box 662)
        - G-M, (6 folders)
        - M-Z, (6 folders) (Box 663)
  - Oversize material (Box OV 664)
    - Scrapbooks
      - 1958
      - 1960-1961 (Box OV 665)
      - 1961 (Box OV 666)
      - 1961 (Box OV 667)
      - 1961-1962 (Box OV 668)
      - 1961-1962 (Box OV 669)
      - 1962 (Box OV 670)
      - 1962 (Box OV 671)
      - 1974 (Box OV 672)
    - Draft campaign literature, 1968 (Box OV 673)
    - Card files of contributions, 1973-1974 (Box OV 674-OV 675)
  - Information about the files (Box 676)
  - Sources of information about Ribicoff
  - Other materials about Ribicoff (collections)
  - Oral history transcripts See Appendix
  - D'Amato, C. Richard, background information, 1981
  - Questionnaires about value of various series of Office Records See Appendix
  - Discarded series, description
  - Miscellany (unsorted)
- 1987 Addition, 1975-1976 (Box 677-682)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, congressional testimony statements and transcripts, newspaper clippings and other printed matter pertaining to the committee's investigation of computer crime in federal programs and private industry.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Government Operations Committee Files, 1975-1976 (Box 677)
    - Abbott, Robert P., testimony
    - Agriculture Department, (2 folders)
    - Allen, Brandt R.
    - Bequai, August
    - Bureau of Prisons, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 678)
      - NIC/CCH Summaries, Leavenworth participants
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Civil Service Commission
    - Commerce Department
      - General
      - National Bureau of Standards
    - Committee bill, L. H. Fountain: HEW Fraud and Regulation Abuse
    - Committee print, Report of Teamsters Local 295 (Box 679)
    - Computer Security Institute
    - Computer, miscellany
    - Congressional Record, reprints
    - Defense Department
    - Energy Resources and Development Administration
    - General Accounting Office, clippings
    - General Services Administration testimony file
    - Health, Education, and Welfare Department
      - ADP Systems Security
      - Testimony draft (Box 680)
    - Honeywell
    - IDentimat
    - Justice Department
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation
      - General
    - Kranzberg, Melvin
    - Library of Congress Congressional Research Service, computer security material
    - Management and Budget Office
    - Navy Department, Subverts “Secure” System
    - Newsletter
    - Nycum, Susan, testimony
    - Parker, Donn B., testimony, (3 folders) (Box 681)
    - Press releases
    - Scantlebury, Don, testimony
    - Staff study
    - Thank-you letters
    - Treasury Department
      - General
      - Internal Revenue Service computer
        - Case, Bureau of Prisons
        - General (Box 682)
        - Ribicoff's opening statement
    - Working papers of Philip Manuel
      - Computer case
      - General, (4 folders)
- 2023 Addition, 1963-1980 (Box 683-694)
  Bound volumes containing select speeches, hearing statements, and articles on a variety of domestic and international issues from Ribicoff's tenure as a United States senator.
  Arranged numerically by volume.
  - "Speeches," 1963-1980 (Box 683)
    - Vols. 1-3 (Box 683)
    - Vols. 4-5 (Box 684)
    - Vols. 6-7 (Box 685)
    - Vols. 8-10 (Box 686)
    - Vols. 11-12 (Box 687)
    - Vols. 13-15 (Box 688)
    - Vols. 16-17 (Box 689)
    - Vols. 18-19 (Box 690)
    - Vols. 20-22 (Box 691)
    - Vols. 23-25 (Box 692)
    - Vols. 26-27 (Box 693)
    - Vol. 28 (Box 694)
- Microfilm Set I: Outgoing Correspondence, 1963-1980 (Reel 1-159)
  Microfilm of outgoing correspondence.
  Arranged by year and therein alphabetically by name of correspondent. Shelf no. 18,138
  - Outgoing Correspondence (Reel 1)
    - 1963
      - Aar-Cly
      - Coa-Fo (Reel 2)
      - Fra-Jim (Reel 3)
      - Jod-Mcw (Reel 4)
      - Mea-Ray (Reel 5)
      - Re-Smy (Reel 6)
      - Sta-Zys (Reel 7)
    - 1964 (Reel 8)
      - Abb-Cap
      - Car-Elz (Reel 9)
      - Ema-Hei (Reel 10)
      - Hel-Laz (Reel 11)
      - Lea-Myr (Reel 12)
      - Nab-Ror (Reel 13)
      - Ros-Thi (Reel 14)
      - Tho-Zyn (Reel 15)
    - 1965 (Reel 16)
      - Aak-Bry
      - Buc-Dlu (Reel 17)
      - Doa-Goy (Reel 18)
      - Gra-Khe (Reel 19)
      - Kic-Mcw (Reel 20)
      - Mea-Pyt (Reel 21)
      - Qua-Smy (Reel 22)
      - Sna-Why (Reel 23)
      - Wic-Zyg (Reel 24)
    - 1966 (Reel 25)
      - Aar-Bri
      - Bro-Daz (Reel 26)
      - Dea-Ghi (Reel 27)
      - Gia-Hyn (Reel 28)
      - Iac-Lev (Reel 29)
      - Lew-Mro (Reel 30)
      - Muc-Rey (Reel 31)
      - Rhe-Sth (Reel 32)
      - Sti-Zyt (Reel 33)
    - 1967 (Reel 34)
      - Aan-Bri
      - Bri-Coy (Reel 35)
      - Cra-Fez (Reel 36)
      - Fia-Hal (Reel 37)
      - Ham-Kaz (Reel 38)
      - Kea-Man (Reel 39)
      - Mar-Nym (Reel 40)
      - Oai-Roi (Reel 41)
      - Rol-Sri (Reel 42)
      - Sta-Wap (Reel 43)
      - War-Zyt (Reel 44)
    - 1968 (Reel 45)
      - Aas-Bri
      - Bro-Day (Reel 46)
      - Dea-Fly (Reel 47)
      - Fod-Gwi (Reel 48)
      - Haa-Jut (Reel 49)
      - Kab-Man (Reel 50)
      - Mar-Nez (Reel 51)
      - Nic-Riv (Reel 52)
      - Roa-Slo (Reel 53)
      - Sna-Vul (Reel 54)
      - Wac-Zwi (Reel 55)
    - 1969 (Reel 56)
      - Aar-Bri
      - Bro-Com (Reel 57)
      - Con-Fey (Reel 58)
      - Fia-McV (Reel 59)
      - Mea-Ozy (Reel 60)
      - Pac-Rzu (Reel 61)
      - Saa-Ste (Reel 62)
      - Sti-Wet (Reel 63)
      - Wha-Zya (Reel 64)
    - 1970 (Reel 65)
      - Aar-Bry
      - Bub-Day (Reel 66)
      - Dea-Fus (Reel 67)
      - Gaa-Hoy (Reel 68)
      - Hrd-Llo (Reel 69)
      - Lob-Mcw (Reel 70)
      - Naa-Raz (Reel 71)
      - Rea-Smy (Reel 72)
      - Sna-Wee (Reel 73)
      - Wei-Zya (Reel 74)
    - 1971 (Reel 75)
      - Aar-Bou
      - Bou-Czu (Reel 76)
      - Dea-Fyl (Reel 77)
      - Gab-Izz (Reel 78)
      - Jac-Lev (Reel 79)
      - Lew-Moy (Reel 80)
      - Muc-Rey (Reel 81)
      - Rhe-Sru (Reel 82)
      - Sta-Wan (Reel 83)
      - War-Zyn (Reel 84)
    - 1972 (Reel 85)
      - Aba-Bys
      - Cab-Dzi (Reel 86)
      - Ead-Hal (Reel 87)
      - Ham-Kyt (Reel 88)
      - Lab-Mli (Reel 89)
      - Moa-Riz (Reel 90)
      - Roa-Stu (Reel 91)
      - Sua-Zys (Reel 92)
    - 1973 (Reel 93)
      - Aar-Boz
      - Bra-Day (Reel 94)
      - Dea-Fus (Reel 95)
      - Gaa-Jis (Reel 96)
      - Joa-Lyo (Reel 97)
      - Mar-Pos (Reel 98)
      - Pot-Smi (Reel 99)
      - Sne-Why (Reel 100)
      - Wic-Zym (Reel 101)
    - 1974 (Reel 102)
      - Aar-Bry
      - Bua-Dez (Reel 103)
      - Dia-Ghi (Reel 104)
      - Gib-Haz (Reel 105)
      - Hea-Kyr (Reel 106)
      - Lab-Miz (Reel 107)
      - Mor-Qui (Reel 108)
      - Rah-Slo (Reel 109)
      - Smi-Vro (Reel 110)
      - Wac-Zwi (Reel 111)
    - 1975 (Reel 112)
      - Aar-Bzu
      - Cab-Dha (Reel 113)
      - Dia-Gol (Reel 114)
      - Gol-Jut (Reel 115)
      - Kac-Lys (Reel 116)
      - Maa-Ng (Reel 117)
      - Nib-Rol (Reel 118)
      - Rom-Sto (Reel 119)
      - Str-Zyw (Reel 120)
    - 1976 (Reel 121)
      - Aba-Byx
      - Cab-Dow (Reel 122)
      - Dow-Gyo (Reel 123)
      - Haa-Kme (Reel 124)
      - Kna-Mcw (Reel 125)
      - Mea-Poy (Reel 126)
      - Pra-Scz (Reel 127)
      - Sea-Tys (Reel 128)
      - Uba-Zyg (Reel 129)
    - 1977 (Reel 130)
      - Aab-Boz
      - Bra-Col (Reel 131)
      - Com-Dzu (Reel 132)
      - Eac-Goz (Reel 133)
      - Gra-Jay (Reel 134)
      - Jeb-Ley (Reel 135)
      - Lhe-Miz (Reel 136)
      - Moc-Pfe (Reel 137)
      - Pha-Sch (Reel 138)
      - Sch-Thu (Reel 139)
      - Tib-Wig (Reel 140)
      - Wil-Zym (Reel 141)
    - 1978 (Reel 142)
      - Aar-Cay
      - Cea-Fly (Reel 143)
      - Foe-Jay (Reel 144)
      - Jea-Maz (Reel 145)
      - Mca-Poz (Reel 146)
      - Pra-Stu (Reel 147)
      - Str-Waz (Reel 148)
      - Wea-Zyd (Reel 149)
    - 1979 (Reel 150)
      - Aba-Czl
      - Dab-Hoo (Reel 151)
      - Hoo-Mey (Reel 152)
      - Mia-Ros (Reel 153)
      - Ros-Waz (Reel 154)
      - Wea-Zyz (Reel 155)
    - 1980 (Reel 156)
      - Aar-Dzi
      - Eac-Kys (Reel 157)
      - Lab-Rez (Reel 158)
      - Rho-Zur (Reel 159)
- Microfilm Set II: Scrapbooks, 1958-1979 (Reel 1-23)
  Microfilm of scrapbooks.
  Arranged chronologically in two sets. Shelf no. 18,633.
  - Scrapbooks, Set I (Reel 1)
    - 1963
      - Jan. 1-Apr. 10
      - May 1-June 30
      - July-Aug. (Reel 2)
      - Oct. 1-Dec. 31
    - 1964, Jan. 1-Mar. 29 (Reel 3)
    - 1965 (Reel 4)
      - Jan. 1-Mar. 31
      - July 1-25 (Reel 5)
    - 1966 (Reel 6)
      - Jan.-Feb.
      - Mar.-Dec. (Reel 7)
    - 1967, Jan.-Sept. (Reel 8)
    - 1968 (Reel 9)
      - Jan.-Feb.
      - July-Aug. (Reel 10)
    - 1968, Nov.-1969, Apr.-Dec. (Reel 11)
    - 1970, Jan.-May (Reel 12)
    - 1971
      - July-Dec.
      - Jan.-May (Reel 13)
    - 1972, June-Aug.
    - 1973, Jan.-Feb. 14 (Reel 14)
    - 1974, Jan.-Nov. (Reel 15)
    - 1975, Jan.-Dec. (Reel 16)
    - 1976, Jan.-Dec.
    - 1977 (Reel 17)
      - Jan.-Oct.
      - Nov.-Dec. (Reel 18)
    - 1978
      - Jan.-Aug.
      - Aug.-Sept. (Reel 19)
    - 1979, Jan.-Apr. (Reel 20)
    - 1980, Jan.-Nov. (Reel 21)
  - Scrapbooks, Set II (Reel 22)
    - 1958, Nov.-1961, Jan.
    - 1962, Nov. 6-1963, Dec. 30 (Reel 23)
Appendix: Oral Histories and Questionnaires
Oral Histories
Jon O. Newman, West Hartford, Conn.
Wayne Granquist, Chevy Chase, Md.
John Andrew Koskinen, Washington, D.C.
Questionnaires
Douglas Joseph Bennet Jr., Washington, D.C.
Ted Leary, Los Angeles, Calif.
Jeff Peterson, Washington, D.C.
Richard Blumenthal, Stamford, Conn.
Malcolm Campbell, West Hartford, Conn.
Arthur House, Washington, D.C.
C. Richard D’Amato, Annapolis, Md.